Tomas Greenpeace

lucky.goldragon@gmail.com

Summary:

Dedicated Blockchain/Web developer specialized in the NFT/DEX/GameFi.

Development experience with DEX platforms, tokenomics,

NFT minting/staking

platforms,

and NFT marketplaces.

Industry experience in web development from

architectural design to

implementation/deployment in both frontend & backend sides.

Work experiences with startups for over years, helping to build technology-based businesses

from the ground up.

Skills & Technologies that I have working knowledge and hands-on

experience in:

- Blockchain
- Smart contract, DeFi, DEX, NFT, Merkle Tree
- Solidity, web3.js, ethers.js, OpenZeppelin
- Rust, SPL, solana/web3, terra.js, Anchor
- Uniswap, PancakeSwap
- ERC-20/ERC-721/ERC-1155, BEP-20/BEP-721/BEP-1155
- Truffle, Hardhat, Phantom, Metamask, Binance Wallet
- Ethereum, Polygon, Solana, Terra
- Frontend Development
- ES5/ES6, TypeScript, SCSS, CSS3, TailwindCSS
- React, Redux, React Hooks, Material-UI, Next.js,

Gatsby, React Bootstrap,

Storybook

• Vue2, Vue3,

Vuex, Vue-Route, Vuetify, Nuxt.js

- Jest, React Testing Library, Cypress, Mocha
- REST, GraphQL, Axios, Hasura
- OAuth2, JWT, Auth0, AWS Cognito

Tomas Greenpeace Figma, Adobe XD

- Backend Development
- AWS, AWS API Gateway, AWS Lambda, AWS CloudFormation, AWS SAM CLI, AWS Amplify, Serverless
- Python, Django, Flask, FastAPI, SQLAlchemy, PySpacy
- Node.js, Express.js, Nest.js
- Azure, Heroku, Netlify, Vercel, DigitalOcean, Godaddy
- Database
- AWS RDS, AWS Data API, AWS DynamoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL
- Agile Development
- SCRUM/Sprint, Kanban Board, Daily Meeting
- GIT, GitHub, GitLab, BitBucket
- Trello, JIRA, YouTrack, Asana, Pivotal Tracker

• Slack, Microsoft Teams, Telegram, Discord

Work History

• Full Stack Developer, Jan 2022 - May 2022, GMIStudios

- DeadHeads
- o The first ever multi-media brand that gives verifiable ownership of its IP to its fan base via NFTs on the Ethereum.
- o Worked on the staking platform that gives duration-based rewards
- o Implement different steps of evolving from DeadHeads, Vessels to HaloHeads
- o Integrated the backend API to create a snapshot of NFT owners using The Graph.
- o Implemented the cross-chained manga airdrop feature (Polygon integrated)
- o Built twitter impact program which boosted user interests into the product
- BountyGames
- o Implemented the next version of Bounty Games
- o Minting suspects, turning in suspects, rewarding bounties to the reporters who reported guilty suspectso Integrated the backend API that generates the metadata and artworks

dynamically

- Twitter Impact Program
- o A SaaS based user contribution chart program
- o Built the frontend using Next.js, TailwindCSS & HeadlessUI and React Hooks
- o Built the backend API using Nest.js
- o Integrated Twitter Login based on Auth0 service

• Full Stack Developer, Aug 2021 – Dec 2021, NextGen

- Worked on various networks including Ethereum, Solana, Polygon
- Developed and deployed 10+ NFT minting/staking platforms
- Implemented all features needed to build the NFT minting platforms including the followings:
- o Artwork/metadata generation
- o ERC721 development/deployment
- o Deploying candy machines for Solana network
- o Building landing/minting pages
- o Integrating minting contract with the frontend using web3.js/Anchor
- o Configuration of start date and timer
- o Presale/whitelist configuration
- o Helping publishing onto the secondary market like Opensea & Magic Eden
- With the fast development of landing/minting pages and NFT contracts and deployment and hosting of the platforms onto the cloud, could bring the platforms into the booming NFT market in a short time and bring the good sales to distributors.
- Implemented staking/breeding/airdrop with ERC20 tokens and SPL tokens as rewards
- Portfolio
- https://pixsol.io
- https://pepepunks.net/
- https://beanverse.io
- https://solmingos.com
- https://thesullens.com
- https://bullsandbears.world/* https://octopusgamenft.io/
- Blockchain Developer, May 2019 Apr 2021, InstaCoin

- Developed token and DEX platform on Ethereum network
- Extended the DEX platform onto Polygon
- Developed a bridge to cross-operate the token on multiple networks
- Integrated contract using web3.js
- Developed wrapped token and DEX platform using project-serum on Solana network

• Full-Stack Web Developer, Mar 2016 – Feb 2019, Funnelair

- Developed internet marketing software
- Improved performance by implementing bulk email sending using asynchronous multiple queues
- Implemented campaigns and campaign designer
- Implemented automated workflow of customer engagement
- Developed membership plan and life-time payment using Stripe
- Developed affiliate program to engage more users

• Web Developer, Oct 2015 - Feb 2016, PABAU

- Developed customer engagement app
- Upgrade the legacy website into the modern webapp using MERN stack
- Improved performance in terms of error-free and speed
- Updated the user interface and added many more features
- Increased the number of active users by 15%

Education:

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science at National University of Singapore